<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.digikam.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">دِجي‌كام</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Digikam</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">digiKam</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxdigiKamxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">digiKam</name>
  <summary>Photo Management Program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Programa per a la gestió de les fotografies</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Programa per a la gestió de les fotografies</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Program pro správu fotografií</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Fotoverwaltung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Πρόγραμμα διαχείρισης φωτογραφιών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Photo Management Program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Programa de gestión de fotos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Application de gestion de photos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Programma di gestione delle foto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Fotobeheerprogramma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Fotohandsamingsprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie zdjęciami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Programa de Gestão de Fotografias</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Program za upravljanje fotografij</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Fotohanteringsprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Resim Düzenleme Programı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для керування фотографіями</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPhoto Management Programxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">照片管理程序</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      digiKam is an advanced digital photo management application, which makes importing and organizing digital photos
      a "snap". The photos are organized in albums which can be sorted chronologically, by folder layout or by custom
      collections.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">digiKam je napredna aplikacija za upravljanje digitalnim fotografijama, što čini uvoz i organizaciju digitalnih fotografija "klikom". Fotografije su organizovane u albumima koji mogu biti sortirani hronološki, po rasporedu foldera ili po korisničkim kolekcijama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El digiKam és una avançada aplicació per a gestionar les fotografies digitals, la qual fa que la importació i organització de les fotografies digitals sigui una «tasca fàcil». Les fotografies s'organitzen en àlbums, els quals es poden ordenar cronològicament, per disposició de la carpeta o per col·leccions personalitzades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El digiKam és una avançada aplicació per a gestionar les fotografies digitals, la qual fa que la importació i organització de les fotografies digitals siga una «tasca fàcil». Les fotografies s'organitzen en àlbums, els quals es poden ordenar cronològicament, per disposició de la carpeta o per col·leccions personalitzades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">digiKam je pokročilý správce fotografií, se kterým snadno zvládnete import a uspořádání digitálních fotografií. Obrázky jsou organizovány v albech, která je možné seřadit podle data, podle struktury složek, nebo podle uživatelských sbírek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">digiKam ist eine leistungsfähige Anwendung zur Verwaltung von Digitalbildern. Es stellt eine einfache Oberfläche zum Importieren und Organisieren von Digitalbildern zur Verfügung. Die Bilder werden in Alben organisiert, die chronologisch oder nach Ordnern oder als benutzerdefinierte Sammlungen sortiert werden können.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το digiKam είναι μια προηγμένη εφαρμογή διαχείρισης φωτογραφιών, που κάνει πανεύκολη την εισαγωγή και οργάνωση φωτογραφιών. Οι φωτογραφίες οργανώνονται σε άλμπουμ με χρονολογική ταξινόμηση, ανάλογα με τη διάταξη του φακέλου ή τις προσαρμοσμένες συλλογές.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">digiKam is an advanced digital photo management application, which makes importing and organizing digital photos a "snap". The photos are organized in albums which can be sorted chronologically, by folder layout or by custom collections.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">digiKam es una aplicación avanzada de gestión de fotos digitales que facilita la importación y la organización de fotos digitales. Las fotos se organizan en álbumes, que se pueden ordenar cronológicamente, por esquemas de carpetas o por colecciones personalizadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">digiKam est une application de gestion de photos avancée, qui rend l'import et l'organisation des photos comme un jeu d'enfant. Les photos sont organisées dans des albums qui peuvent être triés de manière chronologique, selon l'organisation des dossiers, ou par collections personnalisées.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">digiKam é un aplicativo de administración avanzada de fotografía dixital que facilita a importación e organización de fotografías dixitais. As fotos organízanse en álbums, que poden ordenarse de maneira cronolóxica, por distribución do cartafol ou por coleccións personalizadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">digiKam è un'applicazione per la gestione avanzata delle fotografie digitali, che permette di importare e organizzare le proprie foto in pochi clic. Le foto sono organizzate in album, i quali possono essere ordinati per data, per disposizione delle cartelle o per raccolte personalizzate.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">digiKam은 디지털 사진을 가져오고 관리하는 고급 디지털 사진 관리 프로그램입니다. 사진은 시간순, 폴더별 등 다양한 방법으로 정리할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">digiKam is een geavanceerde toepassing voor beheer van digitale foto's, die importeren en organiseren van digitale foto's een "fluitje van een cent" maakt. De foto's zijn georganiseerd in albums die chronologisch, op indeling van mappen of op eigen verzamelingen gesorteerd kunnen zijn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">digiKam er eit avansert fotohandsamingsprogram som gjer det kjapt og enkelt å importera og organisera digitale bilete. Bileta vert ordna i album, som kan sorterast kronologisk, etter mappestruktur eller eigendefinerte samlingar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">digiKam jest zaawansowanym programem do zarządzania cyfrowymi zdjęciami, który czyni importowanie i zarządzanie cyfrowymi zdjęciami "drobnostką". Zdjęcia są urządzone w albumy, które można przechowywać chronologicznie, według układu katalogów lub według własnych zbiorów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O digiKam é uma aplicação de gestão de fotografias digitais, o que torna a importação e a organização de fotografias digitais extremamente simples. As fotos são organizadas em álbuns, os quais podem ser ordenados de forma cronológica, por disposição das pastas ou com colecções personalizadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">DigiKam é um aplicativo para gerenciamento de fotos digitais avançado, que torna muito fácil a importação e organização das suas fotos digitais. As fotos são organizadas em álbuns e ordenadas de forma cronológica, por layout de pastas ou por coleções personalizadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">digiKam je pokročilá aplikácia na správu digitálnych fotografií, ktorá zjednodušuje import a správu digitálnych fotografií. Fotografie sú organizované v albumoch, ktoré sa dajú triediť chronologicky, podľa rozloženia priečinkov alebo podľa vlastných zbierok.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">digiKam je napreden program za upravljanje digitalnih fotografij, ki močno poenostavi uvažanje in organiziranje digitalnih fotografij. Fotografije so organizirane v albumih, ki jih lahko razvrstite po času, razporedu map ali zbirkah po meri.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Digikam är ett avancerat program för hantering av digitala foton, som gör det enkelt att importera och organisera digitala foton. Fotona organiseras i album som kan sorteras kronologiskt, enligt katalogutläggning eller enligt egna samlingar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">digiKam, resimlerinizi içe aktarma ve düzenlemeyi aniden yapmanızı sağlayan bir gelişmiş resim yönetme uygulamasıdır. Resimleriniz albümlerde düzenlenir ve bu albümler tarihe göre sıralanıp, dizin düzeninde ya da özelleşmiş koleksiyonlarda gösterilebilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">digiKam — програма з розширеними можливостями щодо керування цифровими фотографіями, яка робить імпортування і впорядкування цифрових фотографій зовсім простою справою". Програма впорядковує фотографії за альбомами, які можна розташовувати у вікні програму у хронологічному порядку, за теками або за нетиповими збірками.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxdigiKam is an advanced digital photo management application, which makes importing and organizing digital photos a "snap". The photos are organized in albums which can be sorted chronologically, by folder layout or by custom collections.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">الميزات:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Svojstva:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Funksjonar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organization of photos in albums and sub-albums (with tags and comments support)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تنظيم الصّور في ألبومات وألبومات فرعيّة (بدعم الوسوم والتّعليقات)</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Organizacija fotografija u albume i podalbume (sa podrškom za označavanje i komentarisanje)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Organització de les fotografies en àlbums i subàlbums (amb implementació per a les etiquetes i comentaris)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Organització de les fotografies en àlbums i subàlbums (amb implementació per a les etiquetes i comentaris)</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Organizace fotografií do alb a podřízených alb s podporou značek a komentářů</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Organisation von Fotos in Alben und Unteralben mit Unterstützung für Stichwörter und Kommentare</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Οργάνωση φωτογραφιών σε άλμπουμ και υπο-άλμπουμ (με υποστήριξη για ετικέτες και σχόλια)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Organisation of photos in albums and sub-albums (with tags and comments support)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Organización de fotos en álbumes y álbumes anidados (con uso de etiquetas y comentarios)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Organisation de photos en albums et sous-albums (avec prise en charge des étiquettes et des commentaires)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Organización de fotos en álbums e subálbums (con funcionalidade de etiquetas e comentarios).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Organizzazione di foto in album e sotto-album (con supporto per le etichette e i commenti)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">앨범 및 하위 앨범으로 사진 정렬(태그와 주석 지원)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Organiseren van foto's in albums en sub-albums (met tags en ondersteuning van commentaar)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Organisering av bilete i album og underalbum (med støtte for merkelappar og kommentarar)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Grupowanie zdjęć w albumy i podalbumów (z obsługą znaczników i komentarzy)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Organização das fotografias por álbuns e sub-álbuns (com o suporte para marcas e comentários)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Organização de fotos em álbuns e subálbuns (com suporte a etiquetas e comentários)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Organizácia fotiek v albumoch a podalbumoch (so značkami a komentármi)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Organizacija fotografij v albumih in pod-albumih (s podporo oznakam in opombam)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Organisation av foton i album och delalbum (med stöd för etiketter och kommentarer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Resimler albüm ya da alt albümlerde düzenleme (etiket ve yorum desteğiyle)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">упорядковування фотографій за альбомами і підальбомами з підтримкою міток та коментарів;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxOrganization of photos in albums and sub-albums (with tags and comments support)xx</li>
      <li>Support for Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Podrška za Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació per a notes EXIF, IPTC, XMP i del fabricant</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Implementació per a notes EXIF, IPTC, XMP i del fabricant</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podpora pro Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Exif, Iptc, Xmp und Herstellerbemerkungen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Uso de Exif, Iptc, Xmp y notas del fabricante</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge des données EXIF, IPTC, XMP, MakerNotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatíbel con Exif, Iptc, Xmp e Makernotes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">EXIF, IPTC, XMP, 메이커 노트 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Støtte for for Exif, Iptc, Xmp og Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa Exif, Iptc, Xmp, notatek twórcy</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para o EXIF, IPTC, XMP e notas do fabricante</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a EXIF, IPTC, XMP e Notas do Fabricante</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка метаданных EXIF, IPTC, XMP и MakerNote</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora pre Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för EXIF, IPTC, XMP, tillverkaranteckningar</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotesxx</li>
      <li>SQLite or Mysql powered storage for the album contents and its metadata with advanced search tools</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Emmagatzematge basat en SQLite o Mysql per als continguts dels àlbums i les seves metadades amb eines de cerca avançades</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Emmagatzematge basat en SQLite o Mysql per als continguts dels àlbums i les seues metadades amb eines de busca avançades</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Ukládání informace o albech do databáze založené na SQLite nebo MySQL s pokročilými vyhledávacími nástroji</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αποθηκευτικός χώρος με SQLite ή Mysql για τα άλμπουμ και τα μεταδεδομένα τους με προηγμένα εργαλεία αναζήτησης</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">SQLite or Mysql powered storage for the album contents and its metadata with advanced search tools</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Almacenamiento basado en SQLite o Mysql para los álbumes y sus metadatos con herramientas de búsqueda avanzadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Stockage du contenu des albums et des métadonnées fonctionnant avec SQLite ou MySQL et des outils de recherche avancée</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Memorizzazione del contenuto degli album e dei suoi metadati fornita da SQLite o Mysql, con strumenti di ricerca avanzati</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Op SQLite of Mysql gebaseerde opslag voor de inhoud van albums en zijn metagegevens met geavanceerde zoekhulpmiddellen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przechowalnia dla albumów i ich metadanych z zaawansowanymi narzędziami wyszukiwania jest napędzana SQLite lub Mysql</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Armazenamento baseado em SQLite ou MySQL para o conteúdo dos álbuns e os seus meta-dados com ferramentas de pesquisa avançadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Shramba SQLite ali Mysql za albume in metapodatke ter napredna iskalna orodja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Lagring driven av SQLite eller MySQL för album och deras metadata med avancerade sökverktyg</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Albüm içeriği ve meta verileri için gelişmiş arama araçlarıyla, SQLite veya Mysql destekli depolama</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">сховище даних на основі SQLite або MySQL для вмісту альбомів та метаданих із розширеними можливостями пошуку;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSQLite or Mysql powered storage for the album contents and its metadata with advanced search toolsxx</li>
      <li>Support for filtering and sorting albums</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">دعم ترشيح الألبومات وفرزها</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Podrška za filtriranje i sortiranje albuma</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació pel filtratge i classificació dels àlbums</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Implementació pel filtratge i classificació dels àlbums</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podpora řazení a filtrování alb</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für das Filtern und Sortieren von Alben</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για φιλτράρισμα και ταξινόμηση των άλμπουμ</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for filtering and sorting albums</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de filtrado y ordenación de álbumes</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge du filtrage et du tri des albums</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite filtrar e ordenar os álbums.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per il filtraggio e l'ordinamento degli album</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">앨범 필터링 및 정렬</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor filtering en sorteren van albums</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Støtte for filtrering og sortering av album</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa filtrowania i sortowania albumów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para filtrar e ordenar os álbuns</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a filtragem e ordenação de álbuns</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora pre filtrovanie a triedenie albumov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora filtriranju in razvrščanju albumov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för filtrering och sortering av album</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Albümleri filtreleme ve sıralama desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка фільтрування та упорядковування альбомів;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for filtering and sorting albumsxx</li>
      <li>Import from more than 1100 digital camera devices</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">الاستيراد من أكثر من 1100 كمرة رقميّة</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Uvoz iz više od 1100 digitalnih kamera uređaja</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importa des de més de 1.100 dispositius de càmeres digitals</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Importa des de més de 1.100 dispositius de càmeres digitals</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Import z více než 1100 typů digitálních fotoaparátů</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Import von mehr als 1100 digitalen Kameras</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εισαγωγή από περισσότερες από 1100 ψηφιακές κάμερες</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Import from more than 1100 digital camera devices</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite importar de más de 1100 cámaras digitales</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Importe à partir de plus de 1100 appareils photos numériques</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite importar desde máis de 1100 dispositivos de cámara dixital.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Importazione da più di 1.100 dispositivi fotografici digitali</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">1100종 이상의 디지털 카메라에서 사진 가져오기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Importeren uit meer dan 1100 digitale camera's</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Støtte for importering av bilete frå meir enn 1 100 digitalkamera</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Importowanie z więcej niż 1100 aparatów cyfrowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importar a partir de mais de 1100 máquinas digitais</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importação de mais de 1.100 câmeras digitais</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Import z viac ako 1100 digitálnych fotoaparátov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Uvažanje iz več kot 1100 digitalnih fotoaparatov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Import från mer än 1100 digitalkameror</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">1100den fazla kamera cihazından içe aktarma</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість імпортування даних з понад 1100 цифрових фотоапаратів;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImport from more than 1100 digital camera devicesxx</li>
      <li>Support for more than 900 RAW format pictures</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Admet més de 900 formats d'imatge RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Admet més de 900 formats d'imatge RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podpora více než 900 obrázků ve formátu RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για περισσότερους από 900 τύπους RAW εικόνων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for more than 900 RAW format pictures</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite imágenes en más de 900 formatos RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de plus de 900 formats d'image RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per più di 900 immagini in formato RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor 900 RAW-format afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa dla więcej niż 900 postaci zdjęć RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para mais de 900 formatos de imagens RAW</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora več kot 900 vrstam surovih slik (RAW)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för 900 obehandlade bildformat</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">900'den fazla RAW biçimli resim desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка понад 900 форматів цифрових негативів (RAW);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for more than 900 RAW format picturesxx</li>
      <li>Light Table to compare photo side by side</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Taula de llum per a comparar les fotografies costat a costat</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Taula de llum per a comparar les fotografies costat a costat</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Prohlížecí stolek pro porovnání fotografií vedle sebe</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Ελαφρύς πίνακας για σύγκριση φωτογραφιών κατ' αντιπαράθεση</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Light Table to compare photo side by side</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Mesa de luz para comparar fotos una junto a otra</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Table lumineuse pour comparer des photos côte-à-côte</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Tavolo luminoso per confrontare le foto fianco a fianco</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Lichttafel om foto's naast elkaar te vergelijken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Podświetlarka do porównywania zdjęć jedno obok drugiego</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mesa de Luz para comparar as fotografias lado-a-lado</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Osvetlitvena miza za primerjavo fotografij</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ljusbord för att jämföra foton sida vid sida</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Fotoğrafı yan yana karşılaştırmak için Tabloyu Işıklandır</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">стіл із підсвічуванням для порівняння фотографій;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLight Table to compare photo side by sidexx</li>
      <li>Extended features using extra tools</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Funcionalitats ampliades usant eines extres</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Funcionalitats ampliades usant eines extres</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Rozšířené vlastnosti pomocí extra nástrojů</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Επεκτάσεις χαρακτηριστικών με χρήση επιπλέον εργαλείων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Extended features using extra tools</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Funciones extendidas mediante herramientas adicionales</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités étendues par des outils externes</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Funzionalità estese tramite strumenti aggiuntivi</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Uitgebreide mogelijkheden met extra hulpmiddelen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Rozszerzone funkcje używające dodatkowych narzędzi</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades estendidas com ferramentas extra</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Razširjene zmožnosti preko dodatnih orodij</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Utökade funktioner med användning av extra verktyg</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Ekstra araçlar kullanan genişletilmiş özellikler</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">розширення можливостей за допомогою додаткових інструментів;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxExtended features using extra toolsxx</li>
      <li>Share your photos using HTML or publishing them to remote web services</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Compartiu les vostres fotografies usant HTML o publicant-les a serveis web remots</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Compartiu les vostres fotografies usant HTML o publicant-les a serveis web remots</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Sdílení fotografií vytvořením HTML galerie nebo přímým publikováním na vzdálených webových službách</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Μοιραστείτε τις φωτογραφίες σας με HTML ή με δημοσίευση σε απομακρυσμένες υπηρεσίες ιστού</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Share your photos using HTML or publishing them to remote web services</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Compartir fotos usando HTML o publicándolas en servicios web remotos</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Permet de partager vos photos avec des pages HTML ou de les publier sur des services web distants</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Condivisione delle foto tramite HTML o loro pubblicazione nei servizi web remoti</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Uw foto's delen met HTML of ze publiceren op websites op afstand</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Udostępnianie zdjęć przy użyciu HTML lub publikowanie ich poprzez usługi sieciowe</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Partilhar as suas fotos por HTML ou publicá-las em serviços Web remotos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Delite vaše fotografije s pomočjo HTML-ja ali pa jih objavite na oddaljenih storitvah</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Dela foton genom att använda HTML eller publicera dem på webbtjänster</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Resimlerinizi HTML kullanarak paylaşın veya onları uzak web servislerinde yayımlayın</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість оприлюднення фотографій на віддалених службах у інтернеті;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxShare your photos using HTML or publishing them to remote web servicesxx</li>
      <li>Image editor included with advanced tools to fix photo quickly</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Inclou un editor d'imatges amb eines avançades per esmenar ràpidament les fotografies</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Inclou un editor d'imatges amb eines avançades per esmenar ràpidament les fotografies</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Editor obrázků zahrnutý v pokročilých nástrojích pro rychlé opravy fotek</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Περιλαμβάνεται επεξεργαστής εικόνων με προηγμένα εργαλεία για γρήγορη διόρθωση φωτογραφιών</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Image editor included with advanced tools to fix photo quickly</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Editor de imágenes incluido con herramientas avanzadas para corregir las fotos de forma rápida</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Éditeur d'images inclus, avec des fonctionnalités pour réparer rapidement une photo</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Editor delle immagini con strumenti avanzati inclusi per la correzione rapida delle foto</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bewerker van afbeeldingen met geavanceerde hulpmiddelen om foto's snel te repareren</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dołączony edytor obrazów o zaawansowanych narzedziach do szybkiego poprawiania zdjęć</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Editor de imagens que inclui ferramentas avançadas para corrigir rapidamente as fotografias</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vgrajen urejevalnik slik z naprednimi orodji za hitre popravke fotografij</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Bildeditor med avancerade funktioner ingår för att snabbt förbättra foton</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Fotoğrafı hızla düzeltmek için gelişmiş araçlar içeren resim editörü</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">редактор зображень із додатковими можливостями для швидкого виправлення фотографій;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImage editor included with advanced tools to fix photo quicklyxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.digikam.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=digikam</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-graphics/digikam/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/digikam.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <developer_name>digiKam Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ar">مشروع «دِجي‌كام»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="bs">digiKam Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Projecte digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Projecte digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Projekt digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">digiKam-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="el">digiKam Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">digiKam Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Proyecto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Projet digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">Proxecto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Progetto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">digiKam 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">digiKam-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nn">digiKam-prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Projekt digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Projecto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">Projeto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">Проект digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">Projekt digiKamu</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Projekt digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Digikam-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">digiKam Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Проект digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Projectxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-CN">digiKam 项目</developer_name>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>digikam</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
