<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.showfoto.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">showFoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">showFoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">showFoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Showfoto</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxShowfotoxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Showfoto</name>
  <summary>Image Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Editor d'imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Editor d'imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Editor obrázků</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Bildbearbeitung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Image Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Editor de imágenes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Éditeur d'image</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Editor di immagini</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Afbeeldingsbewerker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Biletredigering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytor obrazów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Editor de Imagem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Urejevalnik slik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bildeditor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Resim Düzenleyici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редактор зображень</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxImage Editorxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">图像编辑器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Showfoto is a fast Image Editor with powerful image editing tools. You can use it to view your photographs and improve them.
      Showfoto is the standalone image editor of the digiKam project.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Showfoto je brz uređivač slika sa moćnim alatima za obradu slika. Možete ga koristiti da vidite svoje fotografije i poboljšati ih. Showfoto je samostalan urednik slika projekta digikam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El showFoto és un editor d'imatges ràpid amb potents eines per a l'edició d'imatges. El pot usar per a visualitzar i millorar les vostres fotografies. El showFoto és un editor d'imatges independent del projecte digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El showFoto és un editor d'imatges ràpid amb potents eines per a l'edició d'imatges. El pot usar per a visualitzar i millorar les vostres fotografies. El showFoto és un editor d'imatges independent del projecte digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Showfoto er hurtig billedredigering med kraftfulde redigeringsværktøjer. Du kan bruge det til at fremvise dine fotos og forbedre dem. Showfoto er selvstændig billedredigering fra digiKam-projektet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Showfoto ist eine schnelle Bildbearbeitung mit einigen mächtigen Basiswerkzeugen. Sie können es benutzen, um Ihre Fotos anzusehen und Korrekturen und Änderungen durchzuführen. Showfoto ist das eigenständige Bildbearbeitungsprogramm des Digikam-Projekts.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Showfoto is a fast Image Editor with powerful image editing tools. You can use it to view your photographs and improve them. Showfoto is the standalone image editor of the digiKam project.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Showfoto es un rápido editor de imágenes con potentes herramientas de edición de imágenes. Puede usarlo para ver sus fotografías y mejorarlas. Showfoto es el editor de imágenes independiente del proyecto digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Showfoto on nopea kuvamuokkain, jossa on tehokkaat kuvankäsittelytyökalut. Voit käyttää sitä kuviesi katseluun ja paranteluun. Showfoto on digiKam-projektista erilleen irrotettu kuvamuokkain.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Showfoto est un éditeur d'image rapide comprenant de puissants outils d'édition d'image. Vous pouvez l'utiliser pour afficher des photographies et les améliorer. Showfoto est l'éditeur d'image autonome du projet digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Showfoto é un editor de imaxes rápido con potentes ferramentas de edición. Pode usalo para ver as súas fotografías e melloralas. Showfoto é o editor de imaxes independente do proxecto digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Showfoto è un editor di immagini veloce, con strumenti di modifica potenti. Puoi usarlo per visualizzare le tue fotografie e migliorarle. Showfoto è un editor di immagini autonomo all'interno del progetto digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Showfoto는 강력한 사진 편집 도구가 있는 빠른 사진 편집기입니다. 디지털 사진을 보고 보정할 수 있습니다. Showfoto는 digiKam 프로젝트의 단독 사진 편집기입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Showfoto; is een snelle afbeeldingsbewerker met krachtige hulpmiddelen voor bewerken van afbeeldingen. U kunt het gebruiken om uw foto's te bekijken en te verbeteren. Showfoto is de alleenstaande bewerker van afbeeldingen van het digiKam project.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Showfoto jest szybkim edytorem obrazów z zaawansowanymi narzędziami edycyjnymi. Można go używać do oglądania i polepszania zdjęć. Showfoto jest samodzielnym edytorem obrazów dla projektu digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Showfoto é um editor de imagens rápido com ferramentas de edição de imagens poderosas. Podê-lo-á usar para ver as suas fotografias e melhorá-las. O Showfoto é o editor de imagens independente do projecto digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Showfoto é um editor de imagens rápido com ferramentas poderosas para edição de imagens. Você poderá usá-lo para ver e aprimorar suas fotos. O Showfoto é o editor de imagens independentemente do projeto digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Showfoto je rýchly editor obrázkov so silnými nástrojmi na editáciu obrázkov. Môžete ho použiť na prehliadanie vašich fotografií a zlepšiť ich. ShowFoto je samostatný editor obrázkov projektu digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Showfoto je hiter urejevalnik slik z zmogljivimi orodji za urejanje slik. Uporabite ga lahko za ogled fotografij in njihovo izboljšavo. Showfoto je samostojen urejevalnik slik projekta digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Showfoto är en snabb bildeditor med kraftfulla bildredigeringsverktyg. Den kan användas för att titta på fotografier och förbättra dem. Showfoto är Digikam-projektets  fristående bildeditor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Showfoto, güçlü resim düzenleme araçları olan hızlı bir resim düzenleyicisidir. Resimlerinizi görüntüleyip, iyileştirebilirsiniz. Showfoto, digiKam projesinin bağımsız resim düzenleyicisidir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Showfoto — швидкий редактор зображень, у якому ви знайдете досить потужні інструменти редагування зображень. Ви можете скористатися ним для перегляду і удосконалення ваших фотографій. Showfoto — окрема програма для редагування зображень зі складу проекту digiKam.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxShowfoto is a fast Image Editor with powerful image editing tools. You can use it to view your photographs and improve them. Showfoto is the standalone image editor of the digiKam project.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.digikam.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=digikam</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-graphics/showfoto/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/digikam/showfoto.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <developer_name>digiKam Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="bs">digiKam Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Projecte digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Projecte digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Projekt digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="da">digiKam-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">digiKam-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">digiKam Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Proyecto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">digiKam-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">projet digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">Proxecto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Progetto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">digiKam 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">digiKam-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nn">digiKam-prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Projekt digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Projecto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">Projeto digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">Projekt digiKamu</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Projekt digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Digikam-projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">digiKam Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Проект digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Projectxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-CN">digiKam 项目</developer_name>
  <provides>
    <binary>showfoto</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
